Emily Morgan

Accounting Specialist - Victory Automotive Group

Wilmington, NC 28401 emilymorgan447_upt@indeedemail.com 910-520-9357

Recent graduate with a M.A. in Organizational Leadership with a drive to see organizations and people reach their full potential. Hard-working, collaborative and personable professional with an eye for problem solving. Over ten years of experience in accounting and financial management in both non-profit and private organizations.

Willing to relocate to: Atlanta, GA - Augusta, GA - Columbia, SC

Work Experience

Accounting Specialist

Victory Automotive Group - Shallotte, NC August 2017 to Present

Expanded original role as accounts clerk into accounting specialist. Supervised accounting employees. Implemented a new operating plan for service department to accommodate increased customer volume with a decreased staff. Assist in resolving internal conflict between employees, implementing new store policies, and human resource needs, including new hire interviews.

Financial Administrator

Global River Church - Wilmington, NC September 2008 to September 2016

Collaborates to create and implement an annual budget. Managed all financial transactions and prepared financial statements. Implemented new management software, including installation, set up, and maintenance. Trained staff and client on best use of software.

Marketing Intern

Wieland Electric, GmbH - Bamberg, DE October 2006 to February 2007

Bamberg, Germany

Advised on marketing materials as they pertained to American audiences and assisted in building marketing presentations for international trade shows.

Education

Master of Arts in Organizational Leadership

Regent University - Virginia Beach, VA January 2017 to May 2019

Bachelor of Science in Nonprofit Management

Liberty University - Lynchburg, VA

Skills

- · Accounts Payable
- Accounts Receivable
- Bookkeeping
- Reconciliation
- Quickbooks
- German (4 years)
- General Ledger
- Excel
- Accounting
- Bank Reconciliation
- Account Reconciliation
- Financial Statement Preparation
- Journal Entries
- Office Management
- Financial Management
- General Ledger Reconciliation
- Interviewing